The call is sounded for the last time!
Zum letzten Mal wird nun Appell geblasen!
For the fight, we all stand prepared!
Zum Kampfe steh'n Wir alle schon bereit!
The Third Reich cordially welcomes you!
Das Dritte Reich seien Sie herzlich willkommen!
my wake koukotsu to
My wake and ecstasy
abisu ni saku dirty reward
A dirty reward granted deep in the abyss
lost mind koukatsu no
My lost and cunning mind
saita crimson I like my scars
I like my scars, strewn with blood
umareta imi wo motomete
I look for my reason for living
dare no mono demo nai watashi dake no mono
Nobody can tell me who I am, only I can
yogoreta sekai he
I walk through a world of sin
You know what 'I' mean?
Ah...Tell me why?
I missing. I lost. Not like myself.
But, saw the light in despair.
Blood to the labyrinth of pleasure & forever.
Bring you down!
Take you down!
No way out!
Right now!
So, finally all the same. Aru ga mama ni
So, finally it's all how it should be
bring you down!
So, finally all the same. Aru ga mama ni
So, finally it's all how it should be
take you down!
no way out!
right now!
kowareta jibun no ochita puraido sae
Even the lost pride of a broken being like myself
motometeshimaeba ii
can still be recovered
mezame no harsh blaze moeru chi ni aizu wo
I look into your eyes, afire with yourself and burning blood, and know
The truth is in your scars...